

RAQUEL LIMÂ

in

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/raquellima7



GitHub: https://github.com/RaquelLima7



Portfólio: https://raquellima7.github.io/raquel-lima-dev/

E-mail: raquellimadev@gmail.com Telephone: + 55 21 98003-1894

Nationality: Brazilian

Address: Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Birth date: December 10th, 1992

Civil state: Single

Full-Stack Developer | Ruby on Rails

PROFILE

I'm Full-Stack Developer graduated at Le Wagon (Batch 540) bootcamp completed in June 2021. Course taught in English. I graduated in law and worked as a lawyer having about 9 years of experience in this area.

I speak Portuguese, English and intermediate German.

Passionate about technology and in constant learning. Looking for new challenges because I have wish of learning for grow my knowledge. My goal is through the technology help to make a better world.

PROJECTS

Link with all my projects:

https://raquellima7.github.io/raquel-lima-dev/#projects

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021 | July 2021

- Udemy
- Learned: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, Bootstrap, SQL, MongoDB, REST among others.

UX Designer | November 2020

- Instituto de Gestão e Tecnologia da Informação

German course - Level: B2

- Goethe-Institut Rio de Janeiro.

Exchange program in Germany | February 2019 to March 2019

- Tandem Berlin

SKILLS

Coding Languages/Frameworks/Systems

Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, Node JS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, Mongo DB, git, GitHub e Linux.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon | June 2021 Full-Stack Web Developer

• Le Wagon Rio de Janeiro - Batch 540

Le Wagon is a French programming school with hundreds of students in more than 43 cities around the world offering the highest quality education in the field of technology. The Web Development course 24 weeks, part-time, learning all the skills of a Software Developer. HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQL, git, GitHub and Ruby on Rails.

Damásio Educacional | January 2019 Posgraduate Degree in Brazilian Tax Law.

Centro Universitário Augusto Motta – UNISUAM | December 2016

Bachelor of Laws

INTERNATIONAL EXPERIENCE

I studied abroad with the aim of perfecting the German language. Course held at the Tandem Berlin school, residing for a month in host Family with interaction in the language with natives and students of other nationalities.

VOLUNTARY

TED Translators - Translator | May 2020 to present

 Volunteer on the TED Translators website, participating in projects for the translation of several lectures from English to Brazilian Portuguese.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Nobordist| Brazil

May 2021 to date

Ruby on Rails Developer

- Main activities: Writing and implementing applications in Ruby using the framework Ruby on Rails. Developing back-end components and integrate them with front-end using the framework Vue.js. Carrying out troubleshooting in appropriate cases.

Souza, Monteiro e Brito Advogados | Brazil/Rio de Janeiro

• October 2018 to May 2021.

Lawyer in the Financial Department in an office specialized in banking law and financial operations and civil liability.

- Activities include analysis and preparation of client contracts, assistance in the financial sector of the office in order to avoid losses, monitoring and supervising fees and reimbursements. Responsible for the documentation for participation in bidding process, as well as for the participation in auctions.
- January 2017 to October 2018

Coordinating lawyer in an office specialized in banking law and financial operations and civil liability.

- Activities included team management in the defense of banks with activities ranging from distribution or hiring to closing the process, including making procedural documents, including recourse to higher courts, holding a hearing and oral arguments, procedural follow-up, meeting deadlines and guidance from the administrative team, intern and auxiliary lawyers. Responsible for being in direct contact with the client, as well as dealing with agreements. Due to the results as a team coordinator and legal knowledge, they promoted the promotion to the financial sector.
- April 2014 to December 2016.

Intern in Civil Law in an office specialized in banking law and financial operations and civil liability.

- Activities included writing procedural documents in general, monitoring processes and deadlines, conducting external due diligence, participating in the hearing and enrollment documents in electronic processes. Due to the results obtained in several favorable sentences, promptness and assistance to managers favored the effectiveness as a coordinating lawyer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Viação Madureira Candelária LTDA. | Brazil/Rio de Janeiro

October 2012 to April 2014.

Legal assistant in a bus company in the civil area with specialization in civil and advisory liability.

 Main activities: Receiving and sending e-mail to customers, organizing the processes, diligences, advising the legal body of the company, monitoring the processes, preparing draft agreements.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: fluent English: advanced German: intermediate